

PROFILE

I have over a decade of experience in the world of accounting with an emphasis on accounts receivable and sales tax. During that time, I have discovered my passion for data. I have an endless drive to break down a complex topic into its components, understand how they interact with each other, and communicate it in an effective way to stakeholders at all levels of an organization. I've written countless queries, ETL pipelines, dashboards, markdown and documents. I'm always looking for new ways to make sense of the world using data.

CONTACT

PHONE: 715-307-4853

WEBSITE:

www.chartsandrecreation.com

EMAIL:

kaleb.c.king@gmail.com kinak63@uwosh.edu

HOBBIES

Data visualization **Podcasts** Reading Website development

KALEB KING

Business Analyst

EDUCATION

MS in Data Science

University of Wisconsin - Oshkosh

2020 - Present

Currently maintaining a 4.0 GPA and completed courses in statistical methods, programming for data science, data warehousing, and communicating about data. Expecting to complete by Summer 2024.

BA in Accounting

Lakeland University

2011 - 2015

Maintained a 3.8 GPA and completed courses in advanced financial reporting, federal taxation, cost accounting, and business law.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Business Analyst

Construction Forms

2019-Present

Design and implement data architecture to support report automation and sync data between systems. Create automated reports for stakeholders at all levels of the company.

Accounts Receivable Specialist

Construction Forms

2016-2019

Collect and process customer payments. Streamlined invoicing which reduced processing time by 50% and improved accuracy.

Accounting Coordinator

Foley & Lardner

2013-2016

Build customized reports in Excel, prepare and file property tax returns, develop budgets, and perform monthly reconciliations.

SKILLS















